// Create store for questions 
const questions = [
    {
      question: "At Andrew Jacksonâ€™s funeral in 1845, why was his pet parrot removed ?",
      answers: [
        'Because the parrot was crying too loud.',
        'Because his wife thought the parrot murdered him.',
        'Because the parrot was swearing.',
        'It is illegal to have a parrrot at a funeral.'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Because the parrot was swearing.',
    },
    {
      question: "Why wouldn't the founding fathers wouldn't let Benjamin Franklin work on the Declaration Of Independence ?",
      answers: [
        'Because they were afraid he would slip a joke into it',
        'Because he was not educated',
        'He was a spy',
        'Because he was not a citizen'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Because they were afraid he would slip a joke into it',
    },
    {
      question: "What was Fidel Castro's favorite food?",
      answers: [
        'French Fries',
        'Ice Cream',
        'Candy',
        'Sushi'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Ice Cream',
    },
    {
      question: "How did Emperor Barborsa, the man hitler named a military invasion after, die?",
      answers: [
        'Died by being shot in the knee',
        'Drowned in waist-deep water',
        'Died from eating peanuts',
        'Died from a sparring accident'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Drowned in waist-deep water',
    },
    {
        question: "What was urine medically used for in medieval times?",
        answers: [
          'As a dietary supplement',
          'As an antiseptic',
          'As a painkiller',
          'As a wound cleaner'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'As an antiseptic',
      },
      {
        question: "What country banned soccer/football in 1314 due to mobb voilence?",
        answers: [
          'Germany',
          'Russia',
          'England',
          'Denmark'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'England',
      },
      {
        question: "Which bird was once worshipped like a God by the people on the American continent?",
        answers: [
          'Eagle',
          'Turkey',
          'Parrot',
          'Crow'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'Turkey',
      },
      {
        question: "Which conqueror was once defeated by a horde of bunnies?",
        answers: [
          'Alexander the great',
          'Napoleon Bonaparte',
          'Genghis Khan',
          'Julius Caesar'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'Napoleon Bonaparte',
      },
      {
        question: "Which cutlery used to be seen as sacrilegious?",
        answers: [
          'The spoon',
          'The fork',
          'The ladle',
          'The knife'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'The fork',
      },
      {
        question: "Why did Pope Gregory IV declare war on cats?",
        answers: [
          'A cat killed his son',
          'He believed that cats were instruments of satan',
          'A cat swallowed his gold coin',
          'A cat saw him naked'
          ],
          correctAnswer: 'He believed that cats were instruments of satan',
      },
]
